lightstoneproperty.co.za 2018-09-26

# Lightstone Property Legal Info

## User Agreement

[Terms and Conditions](https://www.lightstoneproperty.co.za/uploads/general/LightstoneWebsiteTermsandConditionsofUsage.pdf) of use of [www.lightstoneproperty.co.za](https://www.lightstoneproperty.co.za/) entered in favour of Lightstone Property, a division of Lightstone (Proprietary) Limited. 

### Privacy Policy

Lightstone Property, a divison of Lightstone Proprietary Limited (" **Lightstone** ") 

#### Introduction

This policy (together with our terms and conditions of use as set out at [www.lightstoneproperty.co.za](https://www.lightstoneproperty.co.za/) (" **Site** ")) applies when you use the Site or access Lightstone's mobile property application (the " **App** "). This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data and/or personal information (which terms are used interchangeable in this policy) we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. The Protection of Personal Information Act (POPI) is aimed at protecting your personal information and prescribes what we may and may not do with it. POPI created an Information Regulator that checks that companies like Lightstone manage personal information in a responsible manner that respects your privacy. 

Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. 

We may collect and process the following information about you: 

**Information you give us** ‐ You may give us information about you by registering on the Site, completing forms on the Site or by corresponding with us by email, phone or otherwise. This includes information you provide when you register to use the Site, request products on the Site or the App, participate in social media platforms on or through the Site, enter a competition, promotion or survey and when you report a problem with our Site or the App. The information you give us may include your name and surname, birth date, gender, country of residence, closest city, address, email address, phone number, age, photograph, username, password and other registration information, as well as credit card information. 

**Information we collect about you and your device** – Each time you visit the Site or access the App we may automatically collect the following information: 

  * technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug‐in types and versions, operating system and platform, non‐personal browsing habits and click patterns; 

  * information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from the Site (including date and time); products you viewed, purchased or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse‐overs), and methods used to browse away from the page and any phone number used to call our customer service number. 

**Information we collect about you via advertising** – From time to time, we may place ads on third party sites. When you view or otherwise interact with our ads, we and our partners may use various technologies (such as cookies) to collect and store information about you including cookie data and anonymised ID's for attribution and advertising purposes. We use these technologies to help us understand more about our customers and the effectiveness of our adverts. 

**Information we receive from other sources** – We may receive information about you if you use any of the other websites we operate (particularly in our group of companies) or the other services we provide. We are also working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, payment services, advertising networks, and search information providers) and may receive information about you from them. 

**Location Information** – We may also collect information about your location, such as the IP Address of the device you access the Site or the App from. 

**Use of Collected Data**

We may use data held about you in the following ways:

  * to allow us to provide you with our products and services; 
  * to allow us to provide you with other information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes; 
  * to process payment details in order to complete the purchase of any product or service; 
  * to allow you to participate in interactive features of the Site and/or the App when you choose to do so; 
  * to conduct competitions and promotions; 
  * to contact you about products and services you have requested; 
  * to notify you about changes to the Site, the App and products and services we offer; 
  * to ensure that content from the Site and the App is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your device; 
  * to administer the Site and the App and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes; 
  * to ensure the Site and the App is safe and secure; 
  * to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you. 

We may also use data held about you for another purpose, but only where such purpose is communicated to you at the point of data collection.
